發言。
立法會主席。
future non-compliance.
The director of audits report.
Having said that, in the course of examining the audit report.
After examining the observation contained in the audit report.
After a thorough study of written responses, the committee decided that.
詳細調查， by way of public hearings， was not required.
The committee has raised in-depth written questions with the bureau and departments concerned.
主席，這是第十七份報告，由委員會在第六立法會期表達。
我會like to express my appreciation for the efforts made by the government units in providing detailed information for consideration by the committee.
many recommendations in the audit report had called for measures to be taken by these units to follow up on non-compliance and outstanding cases.
It has come to the committee's notice that there were many cases where practices of the bureau and department have deviated from the established procedures, guidelines, or even regulations.
Number seventy six includes seven chapters which cover a variety of subjects on the administration of government programmes, and the provision of public services by a total of government twelve government bureau and departments.
石禮謙議員就政府帳目委員會第七十六號報告書向本會發言。石禮謙議員，Mr President，on behalf of the Public Accounts Committee，I have the honour to table our report number seventy six。
for sports development.
inadequate supervision from the bureau over the departments.
陳建波議員就財務委員會審核二零二一。
Of audit and his team, the committee cannot undertake its role and function effectively.
Without the unfailing support and assistance over the five years, thank you.
to record my appreciation of the contribution made by members of the committee. My gratitude goes to the director.
although these subjects spread over a wide spectrum, certain common problems such as the lack of inter-departmental coordination and collaboration.
The committee have made many conclusions and recommendations to help relevant bureaux and departments overcome these problem and achieve value for money in the delivery of public services.
Issue relating to the record keeping, contract administration and monitoring of public works projects were repeatedly identified by the committee in the director of audit reports.
The committee has also hopes that lessons learned will enable them to improve their governance, as good governance is essential for the effective use of public funds, and the continued delivery of efficient and trusted public services. Lastly, I like.
the committee urges the administration to ensure that all bureaux and departments, as well as government-funded organisations, learn from the audit report and implement necessary measures to correct the shortcomings and to prevent further and
在過去近五 years， the committee has held 57 public hearings on 24 subjects， which range from monitoring of public works projects and maintenance of public rental housing flats to the provision of public toilets and management of fund.
I would like to stress that these conclusions and recommendations are made in a constructive and forward-looking manner. All bureau, department and government-funded organisations should learn from the committee's report, as well as the director of audits' report, to overcome such problems.